Today I pretended to get fruits and flowers for mom
and in the end got her a new phone.  We are the
wave of happiness, my mother was
giving me dose morning and evening for a long time that get me trees, get me
trees, get me trees.  Now the ear was
cut off.  So Buddhadev ji said, let's
bring it today.  When we sold mango and litchi boats,
our first plan was to
bring mom to the nursery.  Where we
saw all kinds of lame mangoes but I
liked Daseri.  By the way,
tell me in the comments which mango you like.  Then Buddhadev ji
also saw some sofas for his new home
and mother planted a complete garden here
and seeing all this feast, my sister
Golu got very angry.  She is saying that from next time I will
not come with this aunt.  But
where was Mata Shri going to stop?  Mom
bought so many trees.  On top of that, I
also got a plant for free from uncle.  This is a
mom of a different level.  Now look, it seems as if animals are travelling in the car and
not humans.  So many
leaves, so many leaves.  Now let's activate the second plan
and go to the mobile shop.
And as soon as I reached the mobile shop, my mother came to
know that the phone was being purchased for me.
Actually, the person who called my mother has
passed away.  That's why we had to
buy this new phone.  Along with this steel
crate.  The rest remains to be seen how many mangoes he
can eat, how many blackberries, Radhe-Radhe.